Oyebamiji Timilehin Kehinde

Atinumo Ishola Layout, Iwo Road, Agbala Itura, Ibadan. P.O. Box 28290 Agodi Ibadan.

Mobile: 08039263718, E-mail: timilehinoyebamiji@gmail.com

Personal Profile

Detailed-oriented Accountant offering three (3) years of experience in accounting roles. Industrious and meticulous with strong history of integrity and reliability. Dedicated to accuracy, efficiency and streamlined operation. Capable in data processing and analysis with hawk-eye attention to details, identifying and correcting errors. Hardworking and quick-learning ability. Dedicated with strong work ethics and resourceful nature.

Career Objective

To build an excellent career in the context of a dynamic organization that will leverage my skills and experiences to deliver quality service towards the corporate goals and objectives of any organization.

Education

2008 – 2014 Ladoke Akintola University of Technology, Ogbomoso (LAUTECH)

Grade achieved: B.Tech Accounting, Second Class Upper

2004 – 2007 Orogun Grammer School, Orogun, Ibadan.

Grade achieved: Senior Secondary School Leaving Certificate

2001 – 2004 Shiloh Group of Schools, Total Garden. Ibadan.

Grade achieved: Junior Secondary School leaving Certificate

1996 – 2001 Ore-Ofe Oluwa Nursery and Primary School, Texaco, Ibadan.

Grade achieved: Primary School leaving Certificate

Work History

May 2020- till date

Account & Admin Officer

T-Poledek Enterprise, Bodija, Ibadan. Oyo State

- Used Excel to prepare weekly and monthly report.
- Communicated with suppliers to reconcile invoice payments.
- Maintained accurate and complete documentation for all financial department procedures.
- Supervised daily book keeping operations with attention to accounts receivable, accounts payable, banking reconciliation and disbursements.
- Manages the imprest account.
- Organized data into multiple spreadsheets to streamline data.
- Reviewed figures, postings and documents for correct entry, completeness and accuracy.
- Safeguarding and banking of cash payments from customers.
- Monitors the movement of stocks in and out of the warehouse.

Mar. 2017 – Feb. 2018

Intern

Water corporation of Oyo State. Ibadan, Oyo

- Worked on projects using knowledge gained in training to put together recommendations for issues.
- Collaborated with professional team to solve workflow issues
- Handled the cash payment of interns allowance.
- Upheld office schedule and calender to coordinate workflow and meetings.

June 2015 – Dec. 2016

Account Assistant

Tempo Starch & Glucose Ltd. Obada, Abeokuta. Ogun State

- Evaluated and improved accuracy and completeness of financial records.
- Issued invoices and receipts to customers.
- Analyzed account information and reconciled financial discrepancies to maintain records integrity and compliance.
- Managed the imprest account.
- Daily update of the bank, petty and main cash books and the daily sales.
- Managed the receivables and payables for completeness and timely payment.
- Monthly update of the general ledger.
- Assisted in all phases of closing and reporting functions including raising journals and preparation of the trial balance.
- Assisted manager with special projects and ad hoc reporting requests.
- Receipt and banking of cash from sales and weekly preparation of bank reconciliation.
- Handled the preparation and cash payment of factory workers.

Certifications

- Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) in view
- National Institute of Management.(NIM)
- Certified Soft Skills Professional (CSSP). (Certified by Applied
- Program Management and Training. (APMT, Dallars).
- International Public-Sector Accounting Standards (IPSAS) for the
- Nigerian Public Sector. (Certified by FKV Associates)
- Exploration and Appreciation of Vector/Raster Based Geographical Information System Software for Water Supply. (Certified by MEAA Spatial Planners and Environmental Managers).
- Entrepreneurship skills, Human relations skills, job awareness skills and Corporate Ethics skills. (Certified by Trustco Resources Limited)

Skills

Administrative support Bookkeeping Finance Account reconciliation

Software

- Working knowledge of Microsoft word
- Working knowledge of Microsoft excel

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 24th of January, 1990. **Gender:** Female

Marital Status: Single Religion: Christianity State of Origin: Osun State

L.G.A.: Egbedore Nationality: Nigerian

Referees

Available on request